Rochester, New York and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO Photographs 6239 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Rochester, New York and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO Photographs
2004- 2004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Garlock, Jonathan
Anderson, Marilyn
Rochester and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO
6239 P
0.61 cubic feet
0.6 linear ft.
Photographs.
7544332
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 21, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 25, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6239: Rochester, New York and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO Records 6239 AV: Rochester, New York and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO Audio-Visual Materials 6239 MB: Rochester, New York and Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO Memorabilia
AFL-CIO; Rochester and Vicinity Labor Council
7544332
- Labor Day Parade - 1996-2000 (1) (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Labor Day Parade 1996-2000 (2) (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Labor Day Parade 1996-2000 (3) (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Labor Day Parade 1986-1989 (1) (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Labor Day Parade 1986-1989 (2) (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Labor Day Parade 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Demos, Meetings, Workers Exhibit (1) (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Demos, Meetings, Workers Exhibit (2) (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Demos, Meetings, Workers Exhibit (3) (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Labor Day Parade 1990-1995 (1) (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Labor Day Parade 1990-1995 (2) (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Labor Day Parade 1990-1995 (3) (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Labor Day Parade 1990-1995 (4) (Box 1, Folder 13)
- 2004 Parade (Box 2)
  - 2004 Parade (Box 2, Folder 1)